President, Office of the; Records ua000
M.E. Grenander Department of Special Collections & Archives
- Website of the Office of the President, 2013 May 2 - 2017 July 17; 16; 83 Captures
  - Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 July 17
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host au.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host tr.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host co.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host ro.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host za.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host id.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host gr.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host www.pinterest.de (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host cz.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host hu.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host payments.google.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host nz.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host schema.org (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host in.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host fonts.gstatic.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host jp.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host s.ytimg.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host uk.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host ru.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host br.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host no.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host accounts.google.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host www.gstatic.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host nl.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host fr.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host pl.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host get.adobe.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host dns: (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host connect.facebook.net (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host vine.co (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host input.name (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host www.addthis.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host m.youtube.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host i9.ytimg.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host www.nyraen.org (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host meinvz.net (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host ualbany.alpinesystemsinc.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host www.xing.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host staticxx.facebook.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host mar.gar.in (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host ct.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host www.adobe.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host es.pn (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host citeulike.org (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host fai.informazione.it (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host ads-latest.pinterest.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host cbks1.googleapis.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host drive.google.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host archive.org (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host cdn.youvisit.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host taringa.net (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host vybrali.sme.sk (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host com.google.android.youtube (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host about.me (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host uqshyy.gi (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host nmnathletics.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host steamcommunity.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host getpocket.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host www.insidelacrosse.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host www.informz.net (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host www.w3.org (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host qr-adv.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host apps.albany.edu (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host meetvibe.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host smb.cdnak.dal.neulion.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host apply.commonapp.org (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host www.atmos.albany.edu (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host code.google.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host www.pinterest.info (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host www.ualbanydining.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: DOC_LIMIT 10 for host mts1.googleapis.com (created 2017-05-19, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host www.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host www.alumni.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host www.ualbanysports.com (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host library.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host alumni.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host asrc.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host atmos.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host bioinformatics.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host cela.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host choose.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host cs.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host csda.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host imls.ctg.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host www.ctg.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host cwig.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host events.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host hr.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host ibl.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host illiad.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host liblogs.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host libguides.library.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host scholarsarchive.library.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host listserv.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host m.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host math.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host omega.math.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host mumford.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host nyjm.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host pdp.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host resnet.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host rit.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host cyberphysics.rit.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host rna.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host slsc.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host uaems.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host uapps.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_ROBOTS for host wiki.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2016-02-11)
    Applied scope rule: IGNORE_DELAY for host library.albany.edu (last updated (created 2016-02-11, last updated 2017-05-19)
    Applied scope rule: BLOCK_URL meg.library.albany.edu:8080/archive/search?(STRING_MATCH) for host meg.library.albany.edu (created 2017-05-11, last updated 2017-05-11)
    Applied scope rule: ACCEPT_URL http://www.atmos.albany.edu/facstaff/wkidd(STRING_MATCH) for host None (last updated 2016-10-07)
    Applied scope rule: ACCEPT_URL http://www.atmos.albany.edu/geology/theses/(STRING_MATCH) for host None (last updated 2016-10-07)
    Applied scope rule: ACCEPT_URL www.ctg.albany.edu/(STRING_MATCH) for host None (last updated 2016-10-07)
    start_date: 2017-07-17T16:55:09Z
    original_start_date: 2017-07-17T16:55:09Z
    processing_end_date: 2017-07-23T00:21:36Z
    end_date: 2017-07-22T17:19:10Z
    elapsed_ms: 433389662
    discovered_count: 2896967
    novel_count: 383574
    duplicate_count: 1260379
    queued_count: 1253014
    downloaded_count: 1643953
    download_failures: 389
    warc_revisit_count: 1260323
    warc_url_count: 1643823
    total_data_in_kbs: 242227760
    duplicate_bytes: 230083618880
    warc_compressed_bytes: 3691503039
    doc_rate: 3.79
    kb_rate: 558.0
  - WARC file for Office of the President - University at Albany-SUNY, 2017 July 17